pokertracker.com 2019-06-24

# Privacy Policy | PokerTracker

####  Last Updated on May 25, 2018

Max Value Software, LLC. (“MVS” or “we”, or “our” or “us”) sells software products and services including MVS's “PokerTracker”, “Holdem Manager”, “TableTracker”, and “TableNinja” MVS respects your concerns about privacy and values its relationship with you.

  * What information do we collect about you?
  * Non-Personal Information We Collect
  * Cookies
  * Sharing Your Information
  * Legal Disclosures
  * Security of Personal Information
  * Links to Business Partners and Vendors/Resellers
  * Managing Your Privacy Preferences
  * Marketing
  * Changes to our Privacy Policy
  * Data Housing
  * How to Contact Us
  * Retention

##  What information do we collect about you?

We request personal contact information (name and email address), when you contact us for support or sales assistance , purchase an item from our website (contact information, as well as payment information), or communicate about a particular offer or product with others on our community forums.

Our processing and transfer of the data you provide is limited to the following purposes: fulfillment of your order(s)/contract(s), extension/delivering product updates/service-subscriptions or licenses, product registration and activation, customer and technical support as you may request from time to time, processing license renewals as requested by you, automatically processing license renewals if you elect automatic renewal of your subscription and internal (compliance) audits and fraud prevention. You always have the ability to decide whether to proceed with any activity that requests personal information. If you do not wish to provide the requested information, however, you may not be able to complete the transaction or obtain full functionality on the site if the information is essential to complete the transaction or functionality.

##  Non-Personal Information We Collect

We also collect non-personal information about the use of our websites, products and services which is retained in aggregate form only. This helps us maintain and improve our offerings.

##  Sharing Your Information

We sometimes share your personal information with outside parties for the sole purpose of providing products or services to you (such as third party infrastructure, business process outsourcers, or financial services organizations), but we will never share your private information for any other reasons. We also make sure all outside parties agree the use of your data is compliant both with our policies as well as any pertinent regulatory statutes. We never sell your private information.

##  Legal Disclosures

In certain instances, it may be necessary for MVS to disclose your personal information to government officials or otherwise as required by applicable law. No personally identifiable information will be disclosed to any law enforcement agency or governmental agency except in response to:

A subpoena, warrant or other process issued by a court of competent jurisdiction; A legal process having the same consequence as a court-issued request for information, in that MVS would be in breach of law were it to refuse to provide such information, and it or its officers, executive or employees would be subject to liability for failing to honor such legal process; or, Where such disclosure is necessary for MVS to enforce its legal rights pursuant to the laws of the jurisdiction from which such information was gathered, and there is a legal basis to do so.

##  Security of Personal Information

We are committed to the security of your personal information and take appropriate security measures, consistent with modern information security practices, to protect your personal information. These measures include, on our web sites and Internet-enabled technologies, administrative, technical, physical and procedural steps to protect your data from misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, loss, alteration, or destruction.

##  Links to Business Partners and Vendors/Resellers

On certain MVS web sites, we provide links to companies with whom we may have a business relationship. We encourage you to read their privacy statements, as they may differ from ours.

##  Managing Your Privacy Preferences

You can manage your privacy preferences or receive answers to any questions about our privacy policy by contacting us via the Support System at [https://support.holdemmanager.com](https://support.holdemmanager.com/) for Holdem Manager, [https://support.pokertracker.com](https://support.pokertracker%20%20%20%20%20%20%20%20%20%20%20%20%20%20%20%20%20%20%20%20.com/) for PokerTracker, or by sending written correspondence to [privacy@maxvaluesoftware.com](mailto:privacy@maxvaluesoftware.com).

##  Marketing

We would like to send you information about products and services of ours and other companies which may be of interest to you and may ask for your consent. If you have consented to receive marketing, you may opt out at a later date. You have a right at any time to stop us from contacting you for marketing purposes

If you no longer wish to be contacted for marketing purposes please email [privacy@maxvaluesoftware.com](mailto:privacy@maxvaluesoftware.com).

##  Changes to our Privacy Policy

We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place updates on this web page.

##  Data Housing

The primary location of our retained data is inside the United States. Our datacenter providers have high levels of security covering their physical and logical systems. We have self-certified under Privacy Shield and are compliant with the data regulations of the US, EU GDPR and endeavor to maintain compliance within all markets where we operate.

##  How to Contact Us

You have the right to withdraw consent at any time where relevant, you also have the right to lodge a complaint with an applicable supervisory authority. Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy or information we hold about you or you would like to communicate with our data protection officer.

  * By email at [privacy@maxvaluesoftware.com](mailto:privacy@maxvaluesoftware.com)
  * Or write to us at: 1385 Ridge Rd. #160, Rockwall TX 75087

##  Retention

We retain information that is necessary in providing products and services to our customers. Information associated with an active license is maintained perpetually for license validation purposes. Other information, including but not limited to purchase history on expired software licenses and server logs, is periodically purged.

Contact [privacy@maxvaluesoftware.com](mailto:privacy@maxvaluesoftware.com) for more specific information on our retention policies.
